Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1268.02, cuid32075; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1268.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1269, cuid32076; 1 fragment 07.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1269)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1270, cuid32077; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1270)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1271, cuid32078; 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1271)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1272, cuid32079; 1 fragment 03.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1272)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1273, cuid32080; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1273)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1274, cuid32081; 1 fragment 08.5 x 16.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1274)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1275, cuid32082; 1 fragment 03.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1275)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1276, cuid32083; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1276)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1277, cuid32084; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1277)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1278, cuid32085; 1 fragment 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1278)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1279, cuid32086; 1 fragment 03.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1279)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1280, cuid32087; 1 fragment 06.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1280)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1281, cuid32088; 1 fragment 04.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1281)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1282.01, cuid32089; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1282.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1282.02, cuid32090; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1282.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1283, cuid32091; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1283)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1284, cuid32092; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1284)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1285.01, cuid32093; 1 fragment 02.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1285.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1285.02, cuid32094; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1285.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1286, cuid32095; 1 fragment 20.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1286)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1287, cuid32096; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1287)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1288, cuid32097; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1288)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1289, cuid32098; 1 fragment 02.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1289)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1290, cuid32099; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1290)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1291, cuid32100; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 27, Item P.NYU inv 1291)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1292, cuid32101; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1292)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1293, cuid32102; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1293)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1294, cuid32103; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1294)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1295, cuid32104; 1 fragment 02.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1295)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1296, cuid32105; 1 fragment 03.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1296)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1297, cuid32106; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1297)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1298, cuid32107; 1 fragment 09.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1298)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1299, cuid32108; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1299)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1300, cuid32109; 1 fragment 06.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1300)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1301, cuid32110; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1301)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1302, cuid32111; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1302)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1303, cuid32112; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1303)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1304, cuid32113; 1 fragment 04.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1304)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1305, cuid32114; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1305)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1306, cuid32115; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1306)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1307, cuid32116; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1307)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1308.01, cuid32117; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1308.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1308.02, cuid32118; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1308.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1309, cuid32119; 1 fragment 07.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1309)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1310, cuid32120; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1310)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1311, cuid32121; 1 fragment 04.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1311)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1312, cuid32122; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1312)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1313, cuid32123; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1313)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1314, cuid32124; 1 fragment 03.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1314)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1315, cuid32125; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1315)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1316, cuid32126; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1316)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1317, cuid32127; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1317)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1318, cuid32128; 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1318)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1319, cuid32129; 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1319)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1320, cuid32130; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1320)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1321, cuid32131; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1321)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1322, cuid32132; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1322)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1323, cuid32133; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1323)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1324, cuid32134; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1324)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1325, cuid32135; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1325)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1326, cuid32136; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1326)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1327, cuid32137; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1327)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1328, cuid32138; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1328)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1329, cuid32139; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1329)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1330, cuid32140; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1330)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1331, cuid32141; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1331)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1332, cuid32142; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1332)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1333.01, cuid32143; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1333.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1333.02, cuid32144; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1333.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1334, cuid32145; 1 fragment 05.0 x 15.0 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1334)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1335, cuid32146; 1 fragment 08.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1335)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1336, cuid32147; 1 fragment 06.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1336)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1337, cuid32148; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1337)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1338, cuid32149; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1338)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1339, cuid32150; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1339)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1340, cuid32151; 1 fragment 00.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1340)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1341, cuid32152; 1 fragment 16.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1341)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1342, cuid32153; 1 fragment 01.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1342)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1343, cuid32154; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1343)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1344, cuid32155; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1344)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1346, cuid32156; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1346)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1347, cuid32157; 1 fragment 02.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1347)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1348.01, cuid32158; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1348.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1348.02, cuid32159; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1348.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1349, cuid32160; 1 fragment 01.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1349)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1350, cuid32161; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1350)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1351, cuid32162; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1351)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1352, cuid32163; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1352)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1353, cuid32164; 1 fragment 03.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 28, Item P.NYU inv 1353)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1354, cuid32165; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1354)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1355.01, cuid32166; 1 fragment 01.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1355.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1355.02, cuid32167; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1355.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1356, cuid32168; 1 fragment 02.0 x 0.20 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1356)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1357, cuid32169; 1 fragment 00.5 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1357)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1358, cuid32170; 1 fragment 05.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1358)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1359, cuid32171; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1359)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1360, cuid32172; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1360)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1361, cuid32173; 1 fragment 07.5 x 09.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1361)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1362, cuid32174; 1 fragment 04.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1362)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1363.01, cuid32175; 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1363.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1363.02, cuid32176; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1363.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1364, cuid32177; 1 fragment 02.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1364)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1365, cuid32178; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1365)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1366, cuid32179; 1 fragment 02.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1366)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1367, cuid32180; 1 fragment 02.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1367)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1368, cuid32181; 1 fragment 07.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1368)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1369, cuid32182; 1 fragment 03.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1369)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1370, cuid32183; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1370)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1371, cuid32184; 1 fragment 05.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1371)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1372, cuid32185; 1 fragment 07.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1372)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1373, cuid32186; 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1373)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1374, cuid32187; 1 fragment 11.5 x 21.5 cm (Box 40, Item P.NYU inv 1374)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1375, cuid32188; 1 fragment 01.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1375)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1376, cuid32189; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1376)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1377, cuid32190; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1377)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1378, cuid32191; 1 fragment 04.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1378)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1379, cuid32192; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1379)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1380, cuid32193; 1 fragment 02.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1380)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1381, cuid32194; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1381)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1382, cuid32195; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1382)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1383, cuid32196; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1383)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1384, cuid32197; 1 fragment 05.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1384)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1385, cuid32198; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1385)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1386, cuid32199; 1 fragment 04.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1386)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1387, cuid32200; 1 fragment 04.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1387)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1388, cuid32201; 1 fragment 11.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1388)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1389, cuid32202; 1 fragment 03.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1389)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1390, cuid32203; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1390)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1391, cuid32204; 1 fragment 02.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1391)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1392, cuid32205; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1392)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1393, cuid32206; 1 fragment 11.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1393)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1394, cuid32207; 1 fragment 10.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1394)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1395, cuid32208; 1 fragment 06.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1395)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1396, cuid32209; 1 fragment 14.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1396)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1397.01, cuid32210; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1397.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1397.02, cuid32211; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1397.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1398, cuid32212; 1 fragment 08.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1398)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1399, cuid32213; 1 fragment 09.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1399)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1400, cuid32214; 1 fragment 06.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1400)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1401, cuid32215; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1401)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1404, cuid32216; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1404)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1405, cuid32217; 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1405)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1406.01, cuid32218; 1 fragment 06.0 x 16.0 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 1406.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1406.02, cuid32219; 1 fragment 10.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 1406.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1407, cuid32220; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1407)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1408, cuid32221; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1408)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1409, cuid32222; 1 fragment 01.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1409)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1410, cuid32223; 1 fragment 09.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1410)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1411, cuid32224; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1411)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1412, cuid32225; 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1412)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1413, cuid32226; 1 fragment 05.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1413)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1414, cuid32227; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1414)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1415, cuid32228; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1415)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1416, cuid32229; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1416)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1417, cuid32230; 1 fragment 04.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 29, Item P.NYU inv 1417)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1418, cuid32231; 1 fragment 03.5 x 01.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1418)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1419, cuid32232; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1419)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1420, cuid32233; 1 fragment 00.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1420)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1421, cuid32234; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1421)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1422, cuid32235; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1422)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1423, cuid32236; 1 fragment 00.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1423)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1424, cuid32237; 1 fragment 03.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1424)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1425.01, cuid32238; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1425.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1425.02, cuid32239; 1 fragment 03.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1425.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1426, cuid32240; 1 fragment 08.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1426)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1427, cuid32241; 1 fragment 07.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1427)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1428.01, cuid32242; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1428.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1428.02, cuid32243; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1428.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1429, cuid32244; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1429)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1430, cuid32245; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1430)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1431, cuid32246; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1431)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1432, cuid32247; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1432)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1433, cuid32248; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1433)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1434.01, cuid32249; 1 fragment 01.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1434.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1434.02, cuid32250; 1 fragment 01.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1434.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1435, cuid32251; 1 fragment 08.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1435)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1436, cuid32252; 1 fragment 11.0 x 13.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1436)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1437, cuid32253; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1437)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1438, cuid32254; 1 fragment 05.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1438)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1439, cuid32255; 1 fragment 04.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1439)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1440, cuid32256; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1440)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1441, cuid32257; 1 fragment 05.0 x 09.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1441)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1442, cuid32258; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1442)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1443, cuid32259; 1 fragment 01.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1443)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1444, cuid32260; 1 fragment 02.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1444)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1445, cuid32261; 1 fragment 02.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1445)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1446, cuid32262; 1 fragment 01.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1446)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1447, cuid32263; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1447)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1448, cuid32264; 1 fragment 01.0 x 01.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1448)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1449, cuid32265; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1449)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1450, cuid32266; 1 fragment 04.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1450)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1451, cuid32267; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1451)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1452, cuid32268; 1 fragment 05.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1452)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1453, cuid32269; 1 fragment 07.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1453)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1454, cuid32270; 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1454)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1455, cuid32271; 1 fragment 04.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1455)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1456, cuid32272; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1456)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1457, cuid32273; 1 fragment 06.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1457)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1458, cuid32274; 1 fragment 05.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1458)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1459, cuid32275; 1 fragment 02.0 x 06.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1459)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1460, cuid32276; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1460)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1461, cuid32277; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1461)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1462, cuid32278; 1 fragment 03.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1462)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1463, cuid32279; 1 fragment 03.0 x 07.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1463)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1464, cuid32280; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1464)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1465, cuid32281; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1465)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1466, cuid32282; 1 fragment 02.5 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1466)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1467, cuid32283; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1467)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1468, cuid32284; 1 fragment 10.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1468)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1469, cuid32285; 1 fragment 04.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1469)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1470, cuid32286; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1470)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1471, cuid32287; 1 fragment 04.0 x 14.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1471)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1472, cuid32288; 1 fragment 03.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1472)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1473, cuid32289; 1 fragment 03.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1473)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1474, cuid32290; 1 fragment 04.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1474)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1475, cuid32291; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1475)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1476, cuid32292; 1 fragment 06.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1476)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1477, cuid32293; 1 fragment 04.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 30, Item P.NYU inv 1477)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1478, cuid32294; 1 fragment 01.5 x 05.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1478)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1479, cuid32295; 1 fragment 02.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1479)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1480, cuid32296; 1 fragment 04.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1480)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1481, cuid32297; 1 fragment 05.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1481)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 1482, cuid32298; 1 fragment 08.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 31, Item P.NYU inv 1482)